35 millimeter slides
Marist Archives and Special Collections
35 millimeter slides
2.1.5.1
Marist College
  More
- 35 millimeter slides, 2.1.5.1
  Box 1585
- 35 millimeter slides, 2.1.5.1
  - Carousel number 8 (continued from previous box) [Christmas; unveiling of Thomas E. Dewey commemorative plaque at Christ Church on Quaker Hill (undated); Bob's graduation ceremony at Pawling High School (circa 1971); Alaska; skiing], circa 1971, circa 1970s; 1 (Box 1585)
    - [Carousel number 8 (continued from previous box) [Christmas; unveiling of Thomas E. Dewey commemorative plaque at Christ Church on Quaker Hill (undated); Bob's graduation ceremony at Pawling High School (circa 1971); Alaska; skiing]: Woman standing by construction; Alaska], 1
    - [Carousel number 8 (continued from previous box) [Christmas; unveiling of Thomas E. Dewey commemorative plaque at Christ Church on Quaker Hill (undated); Bob's graduation ceremony at Pawling High School (circa 1971); Alaska; skiing]: People standing near construction; Alaska], 2
    - [Carousel number 8 (continued from previous box) [Christmas; unveiling of Thomas E. Dewey commemorative plaque at Christ Church on Quaker Hill (undated); Bob's graduation ceremony at Pawling High School (circa 1971); Alaska; skiing]: Snowy mountains in Alaska], 3
    - [Carousel number 8 (continued from previous box) [Christmas; unveiling of Thomas E. Dewey commemorative plaque at Christ Church on Quaker Hill (undated); Bob's graduation ceremony at Pawling High School (circa 1971); Alaska; skiing]: Lowell Thomas walking, wearing fur coat; Alaska], 4
    - [Carousel number 8 (continued from previous box) [Christmas; unveiling of Thomas E. Dewey commemorative plaque at Christ Church on Quaker Hill (undated); Bob's graduation ceremony at Pawling High School (circa 1971); Alaska; skiing]: View of town in Alaska], 5
    - [Carousel number 8 (continued from previous box) [Christmas; unveiling of Thomas E. Dewey commemorative plaque at Christ Church on Quaker Hill (undated); Bob's graduation ceremony at Pawling High School (circa 1971); Alaska; skiing]: Trucks parked in parking lot; Alaska], 6
    - [Carousel number 8 (continued from previous box) [Christmas; unveiling of Thomas E. Dewey commemorative plaque at Christ Church on Quaker Hill (undated); Bob's graduation ceremony at Pawling High School (circa 1971); Alaska; skiing]: Three men sitting together], 7
    - [Carousel number 8 (continued from previous box) [Christmas; unveiling of Thomas E. Dewey commemorative plaque at Christ Church on Quaker Hill (undated); Bob's graduation ceremony at Pawling High School (circa 1971); Alaska; skiing]: Two men sitting together, smiling], 8
    - [Carousel number 8 (continued from previous box) [Christmas; unveiling of Thomas E. Dewey commemorative plaque at Christ Church on Quaker Hill (undated); Bob's graduation ceremony at Pawling High School (circa 1971); Alaska; skiing]: Man holding a stuffed animal goose], 9
    - [Carousel number 8 (continued from previous box) [Christmas; unveiling of Thomas E. Dewey commemorative plaque at Christ Church on Quaker Hill (undated); Bob's graduation ceremony at Pawling High School (circa 1971); Alaska; skiing]: Inside of a restaurant], 10
    - [Carousel number 8 (continued from previous box) [Christmas; unveiling of Thomas E. Dewey commemorative plaque at Christ Church on Quaker Hill (undated); Bob's graduation ceremony at Pawling High School (circa 1971); Alaska; skiing]: Inside of a restaurant], 11
    - [Carousel number 8 (continued from previous box) [Christmas; unveiling of Thomas E. Dewey commemorative plaque at Christ Church on Quaker Hill (undated); Bob's graduation ceremony at Pawling High School (circa 1971); Alaska; skiing]: Inside of a church], 12
    - [Carousel number 8 (continued from previous box) [Christmas; unveiling of Thomas E. Dewey commemorative plaque at Christ Church on Quaker Hill (undated); Bob's graduation ceremony at Pawling High School (circa 1971); Alaska; skiing]: Lowell Thomas, woman, and another man standing in front of icy house], 13
    - [Carousel number 8 (continued from previous box) [Christmas; unveiling of Thomas E. Dewey commemorative plaque at Christ Church on Quaker Hill (undated); Bob's graduation ceremony at Pawling High School (circa 1971); Alaska; skiing]: Lowell Thomas, woman, and another man standing in front of icy house], 14
    - [Carousel number 8 (continued from previous box) [Christmas; unveiling of Thomas E. Dewey commemorative plaque at Christ Church on Quaker Hill (undated); Bob's graduation ceremony at Pawling High School (circa 1971); Alaska; skiing]: Lowell Thomas with a group of people, all wearing hard hats on a lift.], 15
    - [Carousel number 8 (continued from previous box) [Christmas; unveiling of Thomas E. Dewey commemorative plaque at Christ Church on Quaker Hill (undated); Bob's graduation ceremony at Pawling High School (circa 1971); Alaska; skiing]: Drawing of mountains and river in Alaska], 16
    - [Carousel number 8 (continued from previous box) [Christmas; unveiling of Thomas E. Dewey commemorative plaque at Christ Church on Quaker Hill (undated); Bob's graduation ceremony at Pawling High School (circa 1971); Alaska; skiing]: Lowell with two other men in front of icy house], 17
  - Carousel number 9 [The Explorers Club (1908 - circa 1970s); first lunar landing (1969); Africa (undated); Tibet-3 slides (1949); T. E. Lawrence-2 slides (1918); Lowell Thomas, Jr. (circa 1962)], 2 (Box 1585)
    - Beginning of Carousel number 9 [The Explorers Club (1908 - circa 1970s); first lunar landing (1969); Africa (undated); Tibet-3 slides (1949); T. E. Lawrence-2 slides (1918); Lowell Thomas, Jr. (circa 1962)] [: Building], 1
    - [Carousel number 9 [The Explorers Club (1908 - circa 1970s); first lunar landing (1969); Africa (undated); Tibet-3 slides (1949); T. E. Lawrence-2 slides (1918); Lowell Thomas, Jr. (circa 1962)]: Small courtyard], 2
    - [Carousel number 9 [The Explorers Club (1908 - circa 1970s); first lunar landing (1969); Africa (undated); Tibet-3 slides (1949); T. E. Lawrence-2 slides (1918); Lowell Thomas, Jr. (circa 1962)]: Looking up at a building], 3
    - [Carousel number 9 [The Explorers Club (1908 - circa 1970s); first lunar landing (1969); Africa (undated); Tibet-3 slides (1949); T. E. Lawrence-2 slides (1918); Lowell Thomas, Jr. (circa 1962)]: Close-up of a man's face], 4
    - [Carousel number 9 [The Explorers Club (1908 - circa 1970s); first lunar landing (1969); Africa (undated); Tibet-3 slides (1949); T. E. Lawrence-2 slides (1918); Lowell Thomas, Jr. (circa 1962)]: Snowy mountains], 5
    - [Carousel number 9 [The Explorers Club (1908 - circa 1970s); first lunar landing (1969); Africa (undated); Tibet-3 slides (1949); T. E. Lawrence-2 slides (1918); Lowell Thomas, Jr. (circa 1962)]: Man sitting in front of framed picture], 6
    - [Carousel number 9 [The Explorers Club (1908 - circa 1970s); first lunar landing (1969); Africa (undated); Tibet-3 slides (1949); T. E. Lawrence-2 slides (1918); Lowell Thomas, Jr. (circa 1962)]: Close-up of a man's face], 7
    - [Carousel number 9 [The Explorers Club (1908 - circa 1970s); first lunar landing (1969); Africa (undated); Tibet-3 slides (1949); T. E. Lawrence-2 slides (1918); Lowell Thomas, Jr. (circa 1962)]: Lowell Thomas with two other men in front of icy house], 8
    - [Carousel number 9 [The Explorers Club (1908 - circa 1970s); first lunar landing (1969); Africa (undated); Tibet-3 slides (1949); T. E. Lawrence-2 slides (1918); Lowell Thomas, Jr. (circa 1962)]: Room with ceiling to floor window view of snowy mountains], 9
    - [Carousel number 9 [The Explorers Club (1908 - circa 1970s); first lunar landing (1969); Africa (undated); Tibet-3 slides (1949); T. E. Lawrence-2 slides (1918); Lowell Thomas, Jr. (circa 1962)]: Lowell Thomas with two other men in front of icy house], 10
    - [Carousel number 9 [The Explorers Club (1908 - circa 1970s); first lunar landing (1969); Africa (undated); Tibet-3 slides (1949); T. E. Lawrence-2 slides (1918); Lowell Thomas, Jr. (circa 1962)]: A resort in Alaska], 11
    - [Carousel number 9 [The Explorers Club (1908 - circa 1970s); first lunar landing (1969); Africa (undated); Tibet-3 slides (1949); T. E. Lawrence-2 slides (1918); Lowell Thomas, Jr. (circa 1962)]: Lowell Thomas with a man and a woman in front of an icy house], 12
    - [Carousel number 9 [The Explorers Club (1908 - circa 1970s); first lunar landing (1969); Africa (undated); Tibet-3 slides (1949); T. E. Lawrence-2 slides (1918); Lowell Thomas, Jr. (circa 1962)]: Man wearing a hard hat, mining?], 13
    - [Carousel number 9 [The Explorers Club (1908 - circa 1970s); first lunar landing (1969); Africa (undated); Tibet-3 slides (1949); T. E. Lawrence-2 slides (1918); Lowell Thomas, Jr. (circa 1962)]: Man and two boys holding a flying fox], 14
    - [Carousel number 9 [The Explorers Club (1908 - circa 1970s); first lunar landing (1969); Africa (undated); Tibet-3 slides (1949); T. E. Lawrence-2 slides (1918); Lowell Thomas, Jr. (circa 1962)]: Man and woman in fur coats, listening to radio], 15
    - [Carousel number 9 [The Explorers Club (1908 - circa 1970s); first lunar landing (1969); Africa (undated); Tibet-3 slides (1949); T. E. Lawrence-2 slides (1918); Lowell Thomas, Jr. (circa 1962)]: Two men looking closely at the ground], 16
    - [Carousel number 9 [The Explorers Club (1908 - circa 1970s); first lunar landing (1969); Africa (undated); Tibet-3 slides (1949); T. E. Lawrence-2 slides (1918); Lowell Thomas, Jr. (circa 1962)]: Inside of a library], 17
    - [Carousel number 9 [The Explorers Club (1908 - circa 1970s); first lunar landing (1969); Africa (undated); Tibet-3 slides (1949); T. E. Lawrence-2 slides (1918); Lowell Thomas, Jr. (circa 1962)]: Inside of a library], 18
    - [Carousel number 9 [The Explorers Club (1908 - circa 1970s); first lunar landing (1969); Africa (undated); Tibet-3 slides (1949); T. E. Lawrence-2 slides (1918); Lowell Thomas, Jr. (circa 1962)]: Building], 19
    - [Carousel number 9 [The Explorers Club (1908 - circa 1970s); first lunar landing (1969); Africa (undated); Tibet-3 slides (1949); T. E. Lawrence-2 slides (1918); Lowell Thomas, Jr. (circa 1962)]: Very close-up picture of man with a fur hood], 20
    - [Carousel number 9 [The Explorers Club (1908 - circa 1970s); first lunar landing (1969); Africa (undated); Tibet-3 slides (1949); T. E. Lawrence-2 slides (1918); Lowell Thomas, Jr. (circa 1962)]: Men on ship], 21
  - Carousel number 9 [The Explorers Club (1908 - circa 1970s); first lunar landing (1969); Africa (undated); Tibet-3 slides (1949); T. E. Lawrence-2 slides (1918); Lowell Thomas, Jr. (circa 1962)], 3 (Box 1585)
    - [Carousel number 9 [The Explorers Club (1908 - circa 1970s); first lunar landing (1969); Africa (undated); Tibet-3 slides (1949); T. E. Lawrence-2 slides (1918); Lowell Thomas, Jr. (circa 1962)]: Men standing outside of airplane], 1
    - [Carousel number 9 [The Explorers Club (1908 - circa 1970s); first lunar landing (1969); Africa (undated); Tibet-3 slides (1949); T. E. Lawrence-2 slides (1918); Lowell Thomas, Jr. (circa 1962)]: View of snowy mountains], 2
    - [Carousel number 9 [The Explorers Club (1908 - circa 1970s); first lunar landing (1969); Africa (undated); Tibet-3 slides (1949); T. E. Lawrence-2 slides (1918); Lowell Thomas, Jr. (circa 1962)]: Man with backpack, trying to cross a creek; Alaska], 3
    - [Carousel number 9 [The Explorers Club (1908 - circa 1970s); first lunar landing (1969); Africa (undated); Tibet-3 slides (1949); T. E. Lawrence-2 slides (1918); Lowell Thomas, Jr. (circa 1962)]: Man in uniform sitting in chair], 4
    - [Carousel number 9 [The Explorers Club (1908 - circa 1970s); first lunar landing (1969); Africa (undated); Tibet-3 slides (1949); T. E. Lawrence-2 slides (1918); Lowell Thomas, Jr. (circa 1962)]: Man wearing a fur hat], 5
    - [Carousel number 9 [The Explorers Club (1908 - circa 1970s); first lunar landing (1969); Africa (undated); Tibet-3 slides (1949); T. E. Lawrence-2 slides (1918); Lowell Thomas, Jr. (circa 1962)]: Two people wearing large backpacks, crossing from ledge to ledge by using a fallen tree], 6
    - [Carousel number 9 [The Explorers Club (1908 - circa 1970s); first lunar landing (1969); Africa (undated); Tibet-3 slides (1949); T. E. Lawrence-2 slides (1918); Lowell Thomas, Jr. (circa 1962)]: Seven men in suits standing together, Lowell Thomas third from left], 7
    - [Carousel number 9 [The Explorers Club (1908 - circa 1970s); first lunar landing (1969); Africa (undated); Tibet-3 slides (1949); T. E. Lawrence-2 slides (1918); Lowell Thomas, Jr. (circa 1962)]: Penguins walking, Alaska], 8
    - [Carousel number 9 [The Explorers Club (1908 - circa 1970s); first lunar landing (1969); Africa (undated); Tibet-3 slides (1949); T. E. Lawrence-2 slides (1918); Lowell Thomas, Jr. (circa 1962)]: Polar bears on floating ice], 9
    - [Carousel number 9 [The Explorers Club (1908 - circa 1970s); first lunar landing (1969); Africa (undated); Tibet-3 slides (1949); T. E. Lawrence-2 slides (1918); Lowell Thomas, Jr. (circa 1962)]: Snowy mountains], 10
    - [Carousel number 9 [The Explorers Club (1908 - circa 1970s); first lunar landing (1969); Africa (undated); Tibet-3 slides (1949); T. E. Lawrence-2 slides (1918); Lowell Thomas, Jr. (circa 1962)]: Snowy mountains], 11
    - [Carousel number 9 [The Explorers Club (1908 - circa 1970s); first lunar landing (1969); Africa (undated); Tibet-3 slides (1949); T. E. Lawrence-2 slides (1918); Lowell Thomas, Jr. (circa 1962)]: Penguin], 12
    - [Carousel number 9 [The Explorers Club (1908 - circa 1970s); first lunar landing (1969); Africa (undated); Tibet-3 slides (1949); T. E. Lawrence-2 slides (1918); Lowell Thomas, Jr. (circa 1962)]: Painting of men covered in snow], 13
    - [Carousel number 9 [The Explorers Club (1908 - circa 1970s); first lunar landing (1969); Africa (undated); Tibet-3 slides (1949); T. E. Lawrence-2 slides (1918); Lowell Thomas, Jr. (circa 1962)]: Portrait of a man], 14
    - [Carousel number 9 [The Explorers Club (1908 - circa 1970s); first lunar landing (1969); Africa (undated); Tibet-3 slides (1949); T. E. Lawrence-2 slides (1918); Lowell Thomas, Jr. (circa 1962)]: Portrait of a man], 15
    - [Carousel number 9 [The Explorers Club (1908 - circa 1970s); first lunar landing (1969); Africa (undated); Tibet-3 slides (1949); T. E. Lawrence-2 slides (1918); Lowell Thomas, Jr. (circa 1962)]: Close-up of Theodore Roosevelt], 16
    - [Carousel number 9 [The Explorers Club (1908 - circa 1970s); first lunar landing (1969); Africa (undated); Tibet-3 slides (1949); T. E. Lawrence-2 slides (1918); Lowell Thomas, Jr. (circa 1962)]: Large bell], 17
    - [Carousel number 9 [The Explorers Club (1908 - circa 1970s); first lunar landing (1969); Africa (undated); Tibet-3 slides (1949); T. E. Lawrence-2 slides (1918); Lowell Thomas, Jr. (circa 1962)]: Conference room?], 18
  - Carousel number 9 [The Explorers Club (1908 - circa 1970s); first lunar landing (1969); Africa (undated); Tibet-3 slides (1949); T. E. Lawrence-2 slides (1918); Lowell Thomas, Jr. (circa 1962)], 4 (Box 1585)
    - [Carousel number 9 [The Explorers Club (1908 - circa 1970s); first lunar landing (1969); Africa (undated); Tibet-3 slides (1949); T. E. Lawrence-2 slides (1918); Lowell Thomas, Jr. (circa 1962)]: Dinner party], 1
    - [Carousel number 9 [The Explorers Club (1908 - circa 1970s); first lunar landing (1969); Africa (undated); Tibet-3 slides (1949); T. E. Lawrence-2 slides (1918); Lowell Thomas, Jr. (circa 1962)]: Drawn portrait of a man in uniform], 2
    - [Carousel number 9 [The Explorers Club (1908 - circa 1970s); first lunar landing (1969); Africa (undated); Tibet-3 slides (1949); T. E. Lawrence-2 slides (1918); Lowell Thomas, Jr. (circa 1962)]: View of snowy mountains], 3
    - [Carousel number 9 [The Explorers Club (1908 - circa 1970s); first lunar landing (1969); Africa (undated); Tibet-3 slides (1949); T. E. Lawrence-2 slides (1918); Lowell Thomas, Jr. (circa 1962)]: Close-up of a man smiling], 4
    - [Carousel number 9 [The Explorers Club (1908 - circa 1970s); first lunar landing (1969); Africa (undated); Tibet-3 slides (1949); T. E. Lawrence-2 slides (1918); Lowell Thomas, Jr. (circa 1962)]: Portrait of a man], 5
    - [Carousel number 9 [The Explorers Club (1908 - circa 1970s); first lunar landing (1969); Africa (undated); Tibet-3 slides (1949); T. E. Lawrence-2 slides (1918); Lowell Thomas, Jr. (circa 1962)]: Close-up of a man, smoking a pipe], 6
    - [Carousel number 9 [The Explorers Club (1908 - circa 1970s); first lunar landing (1969); Africa (undated); Tibet-3 slides (1949); T. E. Lawrence-2 slides (1918); Lowell Thomas, Jr. (circa 1962)]: View of snowy mountains], 7
    - [Carousel number 9 [The Explorers Club (1908 - circa 1970s); first lunar landing (1969); Africa (undated); Tibet-3 slides (1949); T. E. Lawrence-2 slides (1918); Lowell Thomas, Jr. (circa 1962)]: People standing in front of airplane in cold weather, Lowell Thomas at right], 8
    - [Carousel number 9 [The Explorers Club (1908 - circa 1970s); first lunar landing (1969); Africa (undated); Tibet-3 slides (1949); T. E. Lawrence-2 slides (1918); Lowell Thomas, Jr. (circa 1962)]: Painting of a man, signed by [illegible]], 9
    - [Carousel number 9 [The Explorers Club (1908 - circa 1970s); first lunar landing (1969); Africa (undated); Tibet-3 slides (1949); T. E. Lawrence-2 slides (1918); Lowell Thomas, Jr. (circa 1962)]: Portrait of a man in uniform], 10
    - [Carousel number 9 [The Explorers Club (1908 - circa 1970s); first lunar landing (1969); Africa (undated); Tibet-3 slides (1949); T. E. Lawrence-2 slides (1918); Lowell Thomas, Jr. (circa 1962)]: Snowy mountains], 11
    - [Carousel number 9 [The Explorers Club (1908 - circa 1970s); first lunar landing (1969); Africa (undated); Tibet-3 slides (1949); T. E. Lawrence-2 slides (1918); Lowell Thomas, Jr. (circa 1962)]: Ship on icy waters], 12
    - [Carousel number 9 [The Explorers Club (1908 - circa 1970s); first lunar landing (1969); Africa (undated); Tibet-3 slides (1949); T. E. Lawrence-2 slides (1918); Lowell Thomas, Jr. (circa 1962)]: Hot air balloon?], 13
    - [Carousel number 9 [The Explorers Club (1908 - circa 1970s); first lunar landing (1969); Africa (undated); Tibet-3 slides (1949); T. E. Lawrence-2 slides (1918); Lowell Thomas, Jr. (circa 1962)]: A red, white, and blue flag], 14
    - [Carousel number 9 [The Explorers Club (1908 - circa 1970s); first lunar landing (1969); Africa (undated); Tibet-3 slides (1949); T. E. Lawrence-2 slides (1918); Lowell Thomas, Jr. (circa 1962)]: Two men looking at a type of model], 15
    - [Carousel number 9 [The Explorers Club (1908 - circa 1970s); first lunar landing (1969); Africa (undated); Tibet-3 slides (1949); T. E. Lawrence-2 slides (1918); Lowell Thomas, Jr. (circa 1962)]: Portrait of a man], 16
    - [Carousel number 9 [The Explorers Club (1908 - circa 1970s); first lunar landing (1969); Africa (undated); Tibet-3 slides (1949); T. E. Lawrence-2 slides (1918); Lowell Thomas, Jr. (circa 1962)]: Men looking at paper], 17
    - [Carousel number 9 [The Explorers Club (1908 - circa 1970s); first lunar landing (1969); Africa (undated); Tibet-3 slides (1949); T. E. Lawrence-2 slides (1918); Lowell Thomas, Jr. (circa 1962)]: Portrait of a man], 18
    - [Carousel number 9 [The Explorers Club (1908 - circa 1970s); first lunar landing (1969); Africa (undated); Tibet-3 slides (1949); T. E. Lawrence-2 slides (1918); Lowell Thomas, Jr. (circa 1962)]: Man wearing a rain poncho and smoking a pipe], 19
    - [Carousel number 9 [The Explorers Club (1908 - circa 1970s); first lunar landing (1969); Africa (undated); Tibet-3 slides (1949); T. E. Lawrence-2 slides (1918); Lowell Thomas, Jr. (circa 1962)]: Portrait of a man in uniform], 20
  - Carousel number 9 [The Explorers Club (1908 - circa 1970s); first lunar landing (1969); Africa (undated); Tibet-3 slides (1949); T. E. Lawrence-2 slides (1918); Lowell Thomas, Jr. (circa 1962)], 5 (Box 1585)
    - [Carousel number 9 [The Explorers Club (1908 - circa 1970s); first lunar landing (1969); Africa (undated); Tibet-3 slides (1949); T. E. Lawrence-2 slides (1918); Lowell Thomas, Jr. (circa 1962)]: Gorilla], 1
    - [Carousel number 9 [The Explorers Club (1908 - circa 1970s); first lunar landing (1969); Africa (undated); Tibet-3 slides (1949); T. E. Lawrence-2 slides (1918); Lowell Thomas, Jr. (circa 1962)]: Rhinos and mountain behind them], 2
    - [Carousel number 9 [The Explorers Club (1908 - circa 1970s); first lunar landing (1969); Africa (undated); Tibet-3 slides (1949); T. E. Lawrence-2 slides (1918); Lowell Thomas, Jr. (circa 1962)]: Man and woman with camera], 3
    - [Carousel number 9 [The Explorers Club (1908 - circa 1970s); first lunar landing (1969); Africa (undated); Tibet-3 slides (1949); T. E. Lawrence-2 slides (1918); Lowell Thomas, Jr. (circa 1962)]: African native with spear, airplane, mountain in background], 4
    - [Carousel number 9 [The Explorers Club (1908 - circa 1970s); first lunar landing (1969); Africa (undated); Tibet-3 slides (1949); T. E. Lawrence-2 slides (1918); Lowell Thomas, Jr. (circa 1962)]: On the moon], 5
    - [Carousel number 9 [The Explorers Club (1908 - circa 1970s); first lunar landing (1969); Africa (undated); Tibet-3 slides (1949); T. E. Lawrence-2 slides (1918); Lowell Thomas, Jr. (circa 1962)]: Three men in space suits], 6
    - [Carousel number 9 [The Explorers Club (1908 - circa 1970s); first lunar landing (1969); Africa (undated); Tibet-3 slides (1949); T. E. Lawrence-2 slides (1918); Lowell Thomas, Jr. (circa 1962)]: Space equipment], 7
    - [Carousel number 9 [The Explorers Club (1908 - circa 1970s); first lunar landing (1969); Africa (undated); Tibet-3 slides (1949); T. E. Lawrence-2 slides (1918); Lowell Thomas, Jr. (circa 1962)]: Space equipment], 8
    - [Carousel number 9 [The Explorers Club (1908 - circa 1970s); first lunar landing (1969); Africa (undated); Tibet-3 slides (1949); T. E. Lawrence-2 slides (1918); Lowell Thomas, Jr. (circa 1962)]: Lunar globe?], 9
    - [Carousel number 9 [The Explorers Club (1908 - circa 1970s); first lunar landing (1969); Africa (undated); Tibet-3 slides (1949); T. E. Lawrence-2 slides (1918); Lowell Thomas, Jr. (circa 1962)]: Woman holding African Native], 10
    - [Carousel number 9 [The Explorers Club (1908 - circa 1970s); first lunar landing (1969); Africa (undated); Tibet-3 slides (1949); T. E. Lawrence-2 slides (1918); Lowell Thomas, Jr. (circa 1962)]: Space equipment on moon], 11
    - [Carousel number 9 [The Explorers Club (1908 - circa 1970s); first lunar landing (1969); Africa (undated); Tibet-3 slides (1949); T. E. Lawrence-2 slides (1918); Lowell Thomas, Jr. (circa 1962)]: Astronaut on moon], 12
    - [Carousel number 9 [The Explorers Club (1908 - circa 1970s); first lunar landing (1969); Africa (undated); Tibet-3 slides (1949); T. E. Lawrence-2 slides (1918); Lowell Thomas, Jr. (circa 1962)]: Elephants with mountain behind them], 13
    - [Carousel number 9 [The Explorers Club (1908 - circa 1970s); first lunar landing (1969); Africa (undated); Tibet-3 slides (1949); T. E. Lawrence-2 slides (1918); Lowell Thomas, Jr. (circa 1962)]: Giraffes with mountain behind them], 14
    - [Carousel number 9 [The Explorers Club (1908 - circa 1970s); first lunar landing (1969); Africa (undated); Tibet-3 slides (1949); T. E. Lawrence-2 slides (1918); Lowell Thomas, Jr. (circa 1962)]: Native with painted face and elaborate headdress], 15
    - [Carousel number 9 [The Explorers Club (1908 - circa 1970s); first lunar landing (1969); Africa (undated); Tibet-3 slides (1949); T. E. Lawrence-2 slides (1918); Lowell Thomas, Jr. (circa 1962)]: Native with elaborate headdress], 16